{
    "subject": "resource/Romain_Ferrier",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1976",
    "human_readable": "Romain Ferrier was born in 1976.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8842170834541321,
            "question": "In what year was Romain Ferrier born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8124416470527649,
            "question": "What decade was Romain Ferrier born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7205605506896973,
            "question": "What is Romain Ferrier's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7021378874778748,
            "question": "How many years ago was Romain Ferrier born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6880384683609009,
            "question": "What year marks Romain Ferrier's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.628845751285553,
            "question": "What significant events happened during the year of Romain Ferrier's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.424357146024704,
            "question": "What age is Romain Ferrier now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38166752457618713,
            "question": "How old was Romain Ferrier in the year 2000?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34170451760292053,
            "question": "When did Romain Ferrier enter the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32800760865211487,
            "question": "Is Romain Ferrier a millennial?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Romain Ferrier was born in 1976.",
            "html": "dbpedia_38_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Romain Ferrier enter the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_38_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old was Romain Ferrier in the year 2000?",
            "html": "dbpedia_38_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What age is Romain Ferrier now?",
            "html": "dbpedia_38_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_38_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_38_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_38_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_38_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_38_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_38_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_38_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_38_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_38_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_38_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that Romain Ferrier was born on February 24, 1976."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Romain Ferrier was born on February 24, 1976. Therefore, the statement \"Romain Ferrier was born in 1976\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}